=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الصغير للإمبراطور الشيطاني =
=Episode 6=
= الحلقة 6 =
You're not as handsome as Li Wuyou.
أنت لست وسيمًا مثل Li Wuyou.
You've seen the true face of Wuyou?
هل رأيت الوجه الحقيقي لـ Wuyou؟
There're less than 10 people in Huasheng Empire who've seen his true face.
هناك أقل من 10 أشخاص في إمبراطورية هواشنغ رأوا وجهه الحقيقي.
It seems like you're not a simple girl.
يبدو أنك لست فتاة بسيطة.
This is not right.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
I checked the almanac.
راجعت التقويم.
How could I have stepped on dog poop?
كيف لي أن داس على أنبوب الكلب؟
Could this be a pirated version?
هل يمكن أن تكون هذه نسخة مقرصنة؟
Your shoulder...
كتفك...
It written here that
كتبت هنا أن
I offended the Toilet God today. I shouldn't have gone out.
لقد أساءت إلى الله المرحاض اليوم.  ما كان يجب أن أخرج.
Toilet God?
مرحاض الله؟
Ms. Chuchu.
السيدة تشوتشو.
See you next time.
أراك المرة القادمة.
Why are the people around Li Wuyou so weird?
لماذا الناس حول Li Wuyou غريبون جدًا؟
What kind of people are these?
أي نوع من الناس هؤلاء؟
(After days of observation,)
(بعد أيام من الملاحظة)
(besides having a bad temper and sharp tongue,)
(بالإضافة إلى المزاج السيئ واللسان الحاد)
(Li Wuyou has no other problem.)
(ليس لدى Li Wuyou مشكلة أخرى.)
(Besides, he's good looking.)
(إلى جانب ذلك ، إنه ذو مظهر جيد.)
(He's still competitive in the marriage market.)
(لا يزال قادرًا على المنافسة في سوق الزواج).
(Next, I should find out)
(بعد ذلك ، يجب أن أكتشف)
(what type of girls Li Wuyou likes.)
(ما نوع الفتيات التي تحبها Li Wuyou.)
(But he and Ms. Yueying)
(لكنه والسيدة يويينغ)
(always pull a straight face.)
(اسحب دائمًا وجهًا مستقيمًا).
(It won't work if I ask them.)
(لن ينجح إذا سألتهم.)
Oh, right.
صحيح.
Why don't I have it?
لماذا ليس لدي؟
I remember I took it along
أتذكر أنني أخذتها على طول
when I left Matchmaker's Hall.
عندما غادرت قاعة Matchmaker.
Here it is.
ها هو.
Young Master, I've investigated.
السيد الشاب ، لقد حققت.
The Empress
الامبراطورة
published a notice to find you a concubine.
نشرت إشعارًا لتجد لك خليلة.
Qiao Chuchu was the only one who applied.
كان Qiao Chuchu هو الشخص الوحيد الذي تقدم بطلب.
Hence she was recruited right away.
ومن ثم تم تجنيدها على الفور.
Her name is the only one in the register.
اسمها هو الوحيد في السجل.
We can't find any information on her family.
لا يمكننا العثور على أي معلومات عن عائلتها.
It's perhaps a fake.
ربما يكون مزيفًا.
As I expected.
كما توقعت.
Could it be the Empress?
هل يمكن أن تكون الإمبراطورة؟
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
Mu Huanian sees me as a demon,
مو هوانيان يراني كشيطان ،
but as long as I don't do anything to harm the royal family,
لكن طالما أنني لا أفعل أي شيء لإيذاء العائلة المالكة ،
she would like to think that I didn't exist.
كانت تود أن تعتقد أنني غير موجود.
So Qiao Chuchu is indeed related to Demon Prince?
إذن Qiao Chuchu مرتبط بالفعل بـ Demon Prince؟
It's a tradition that the Demon Emperor's son inherits the throne.
إنه تقليد أن يرث ابن الإمبراطور الشيطاني العرش.
Although Demon Prince is a strong demon,
على الرغم من أن الأمير الشيطاني هو شيطان قوي ،
he wouldn't dare to rebel so openly.
لم يكن يجرؤ على التمرد علانية.
Better an open enemy than a false friend.
عدو مفتوح أفضل من الصديق المزيف.
He's tired of being the second in command.
لقد سئم من كونه الرجل الثاني في القيادة.
Whenever he has time,
كلما كان لديه الوقت ،
he tries to find a way to kill me.
يحاول إيجاد طريقة لقتلي.
Young Master.
المعلم الصغير.
I'll protect the Demon Emperor at the expense
سأحمي الإمبراطور الشيطاني على حساب
of my life.
من حياتي.
(Mixed-blood people always look good.)
(يبدو الأشخاص المختلطون دائمًا في حالة جيدة).
(I wonder which young lady will be the lucky one.)
(أتساءل أي سيدة شابة ستكون المحظوظة).
Qiao Chuchu, you're a professional Little Matchmaker.
Qiao Chuchu ، أنت صانع عيدان صغير محترف.
How can you behave like a fan girl towards your client?
كيف يمكنك أن تتصرف كفتاة معجب تجاه عميلك؟
Unprofessional.
غير محترف.
The task is more important.
المهمة أكثر أهمية.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪